If you are spending your business cash flow on these things,
then I want you to stop because you are wasting your money.
And right now
I am trying to be radically transparent with the business advice that I give
simply because of what I've gone through and all the mistakes that I've made.
Now the more you know. So
the first piece of advice that I would give to business owners
is to stop talking about being a 6 or seven figure business owner
and trying to look bigger than you actually are.
Because the only thing this actually does is disappoint yourself
because you know
the gap between where you actually are and what you are portraying to the world.
And what it also does is
make you spend money on things to try and make you look bigger.
You'll sponsor events, you'll hire a P R.
Agency and you'll try and get into articles to show how big your business is.
The second thing I would advise is to get rid of your marketing agency.
Business owners say that learning ads is overwhelming.
My advice is to spend an entire day watching YouTube videos
and learning how to do it from scratch.
A 20 year old at a marketing agency can learn how to do your ads,
then why can't you?
And the last thing is to stop simply accepting your supplier terms.
Everything can be negotiated from your payment terms to how many pieces you need
To buy, stick to the lowest possible m o q,
and even negotiate that down.
Because while a lower stock run can mean less margin initially,
you could be left with a lot of pieces that will never sell,
and that is a cash flow disaster.
By doing these three things,
you are going to save yourself a lot of time, energy and money.